Try
压制:随Feng
歌手：P!nk
Ever wonder about what he's doing
也曾想过他的一举一动
How it all turned to lies
为何一切变成谎言
Sometimes I think﻿ that it's better to never ask why
有时我认为从不去问询  会比较好
Where there is desire There is gonna be a flame
有了欲望  就会燃起火焰
Where there is a flame Someone's bound to get burned
有火焰燃烧  有人必将被灼伤
But just because it burns Doesn't mean you're gonna die
但就算被灼伤  这并不意味你将会死亡
You've gotta get up and try try try
你要重新站起  不断尝试
Gotta get up and try try try
要重新站起  一再尝试
You gotta get up and try try try
你要重新站起  不断尝试
Funny how the heart can be deceiving
有趣的是心可以如此欺骗
More than just a couple times
明知故犯不知多少回
Why do we fall in love so easy
为何我们如此容易相爱
Even when it's not right
即使这是错爱
Where there is desire There is gonna be a flame
有了欲望  就会燃起火焰
Where there is a flame Someone's bound to get burned
有火焰燃烧  有人必将被灼伤
But just because it burns Doesn't mean you're gonna die
但就算被灼伤  这并不意味你将会死亡
You've gotta get up and try try try
你要重新站起  不断尝试
Gotta get up and try try try
要重新站起  一再尝试
You gotta get up and try try try
你要重新站起  不断尝试
Ever worried that it might be ruined
也曾担心一切终将毁灭
And does it make you wanna cry?
但这会让你伤心流泪吗?
When you're out there doing what you're doing
当你离开去做你想做的事时
Are you just getting by?
你只是玩玩而已吗?
Tell me are you just getting by by by
告诉我  你只是玩玩而已吗
Where there is desire There is gonna be a flame
有了欲望  就会燃起火焰
Where there is a flame Someone's bound to get burned
有火焰燃烧  有人必将被灼伤
But just because it burns Doesn't mean you're gonna die
但就算被灼伤  这并不意味你将会死亡
You've gotta get up and try try try
你要重新站起  不断尝试
Gotta get up and try try try
要重新站起  一再尝试
You gotta get up and try try try
你要重新站起  不断尝试
Gotta get up and try try try
要重新站起  一再尝试
You gotta get up and try try try
你要重新站起  不断尝试
Gotta get up and try try try
要重新站起  一再尝试
You gotta get up and try try try
你要重新站起  不断尝试
Gotta get up and try try try
要重新站起  一再尝试
压制:随Feng